Indiana University President Emeritus John W. Ryan papers, 1944-2011 C456
Indiana University Archives
- Correspondence files, 1988-2011 (Box 12)
  - Alpha Copies, 1988-2011 (Box 12)
    - Z (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
    - X-Z (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - 1996-1998 (Box 13)
      - A (Box 13)
      - B (Box 13)
      - C (Box 13)
      - D (Box 13)
      - E (Box 13)
      - F (Box 13)
      - G (Box 13)
      - H (Box 13)
      - I (Box 13)
      - J (Box 13)
      - K (Box 13)
      - L (Box 13)
      - M (Box 13)
      - N (Box 13)
      - O-Q (Box 13)
      - R (Box 13)
      - S (Box 13)
      - T (Box 13)
      - U-W (Box 13)
      - X-Z (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 13)
      - 1999 (Box 13)
      - 2000 (Box 13)
      - 2001 (Box 13)
        - A-D (Box 13)
        - E-H (Box 13)
        - I-L (Box 13)
        - M-Q (Box 13)
        - R-U (Box 13)
        - V-Z (Box 13)
      - 2002 (Box 13)
        - A-D (Box 13)
        - D-H (Box 13)
        - I-L (Box 13)
        - M-Q (Box 13)
        - R-U (Box 13)
        - V-Z (Box 13)
      - 2003 (Box 14)
        - A-E (Box 14)
        - F-I (Box 14)
        - J-N (Box 14)
        - O-S (Box 14)
        - T-Z (Box 14)
      - 2004 (Box 14)
        - A-E (Box 14)
        - F-L (Box 14)
        - M-R (Box 14)
        - S-Z (Box 14)
      - 2005 (Box 14)
        - A-E (Box 14)
        - F-L (Box 14)
        - M-R (Box 14)
        - S-Z (Box 14)
      - 2006 (Box 14)
        - A-E (Box 14)
        - F-L (Box 14)
        - M-R (Box 14)
        - S-Z (Box 14)
      - 2007 (Box 14)
        - A-E (Box 14)
        - E-L (Box 14)
        - M-R (Box 14)
        - S-Z (Box 14)
      - 2008 (Box 14)
      - 2009 (Box 14)
      - 2010 (Box 14)
      - 2011 (Box 14)
  - Chronological Copies, 1988-2011 (Box 14)
    - October 1988 (Box 14)
    - November 1988 (Box 14)
    - December 1988 (Box 14)
    - January 1989 (Box 14)
    - February 1989 (Box 14)
    - March 1989 (Box 14)
    - April 1989 (Box 14)
    - May 1989 (Box 14)
    - June 1989 (Box 14)
    - July 1989 (Box 14)
    - August 1989 (Box 14)
    - September 1989 (Box 14)
    - October 1989 (Box 14)
    - November 1989 (Box 14)
    - December 1989 (Box 14)
    - January 1990 (Box 14)
    - February 1990 (Box 14)
    - March 1990 (Box 14)
    - April 1990 (Box 14)
    - May 1990 (Box 14)
    - June 1990 (Box 14)
    - July 1990 (Box 14)
    - August 1990 (Box 14)
    - September 1990 (Box 14)
    - October 1990 (Box 14)
    - November 1990 (Box 14)
    - December 1990 (Box 14)
    - January 1991 (Box 14)
    - February 1991 (Box 14)
    - March 1991 (Box 14)
    - April 1991 (Box 14)
    - May 1991 (Box 14)
    - June 1991 (Box 14)
    - July 1991 (Box 14)
    - August 1991 (Box 14)
    - September 1991 (Box 14)
    - October, November, December 1991 (Box 14)
    - January-February 1992 (Box 14)
    - March-April 1992 (Box 14)
    - April 1992 (Box 14)
    - May-June 1992 (Box 14)
    - July, August, September, 1992 (Box 14)
    - October, November, December 1992 (Box 14)
    - January, February, March, 1993 (Box 14)
    - April- May 1993 (Box 14)
    - June- July 1993 (Box 14)
    - August-September 1993 (Box 14)
    - October, November, December 1993 (Box 14)
    - January-February 1994 (Box 14)
    - March-April 1994 (Box 14)
    - May, June, July August, 1994 (Box 14)
    - September-October 1994 (Box 15)
    - November-December 1994 (Box 15)
    - January-February 1995 (Box 15)
    - March-April 1995 (Box 15)
    - May-June 1995 (Box 15)
    - July August, September, 1995 (Box 15)
    - October, November, December 1995 (Box 15)
    - January, February, March, 1996 (Box 15)
    - April, May, June 1996 (Box 15)
    - July August, September, 1996 (Box 15)
    - October, November, December 1996 (Box 15)
    - January, February, March, 1997 (Box 15)
    - April, May, June 1997 (Box 15)
    - July August, September, 1997 (Box 15)
    - October, November, December 1997 (Box 15)
    - 1998 (Box 15)
    - 1999 (Box 15)
    - 2000 (Box 15)
    - 2001 (Box 15)
      - January-March (Box 15)
      - April-June (Box 15)
      - July-September (Box 15)
      - October-December (Box 15)
    - 2002 (Box 15)
      - January-April (Box 15)
      - May-August (Box 15)
      - September-December (Box 15)
    - 2003 (Box 15)
      - January-May (Box 15)
      - June-August (Box 15)
      - September-December (Box 15)
    - 2004 (Box 15)
      - January-June (Box 15)
      - July-December (Box 15)
    - 2005 (Box 15)
      - January-April (Box 15)
      - May-August (Box 15)
      - September-December (Box 15)
    - 2006 (Box 15)
      - January-June (Box 15)
      - July-October (Box 15)
      - November-December (Box 15)
    - 2007 (Box 15)
      - January-April (Box 15)
      - May-August (Box 15)
      - September-December (Box 15)
    - 2008 (Box 15)
      - January-June (Box 15)
      - July-December (Box 15)
    - 2009 (Box 15)
    - 2010 (Box 15)
    - 2011 (Box 15)
- Travel Files, 1988-2006
  - SUNY: Russia--Poland--UK, October 27-November 6, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Travel- Moscow, Russia (SUNY) State University, January 22-26, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Salzburg Seminar, 1996-2002 (Box 15)
    - Educational Reform in South Africa Salzburg, Austria, May 3-13, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Kaunas University of Technology, 2000 (Box 15)
    - Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology, November 27-December 1, 2000 (Box 15)
    - Report, Adam Mickiewicz University Poznan, Poland, February 18-22, 2002 (Box 15)
    - Seminar- and Poznan, February 13-17, 2001; February 18-22, 2002 (Box 15)
    - University of Latvia, Riga, Latvia, April 22-26, 2001 (Box 15)
  - "Universities in the New Millennium" Bogazici University, Istanbul, Turkey (for SUNY), October 12-14, 2000 (Box 15)
  - University of Latvia: reports and statistics, 1996-2000 (Box 15)
  - Hungarian Accreditation, Committee (Box 16)
    - Board Meeting (HAC), Budapest, Hungary, March 3-5, 1996 (Box 16)
    - Budapest, Hungary, Feb. 25-28, 1995 (Box 16)
  - Celebration of the 75th Anniversary of the founding of Nankai University Tianjin, PR China, October 16, 1994 (Box 16)
  - Cre-Columbus Seminar Paper, September, 1994 (Box 16)
  - Regional Campus: IUPUI Southeast Asia Program Vietnam Trip, August, 1994 (Box 16)
  - Travel to Vietnam from Papua New Guinea Information (& Other) for, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Opening Ceremony_ Engineering Program in Bangi, Malaysia(Tenaga Nasional Berhad) July 9, 1994 (Box 16)
  - Foreign Travel: Hungarian Accreditation Committee Advisory Board Budapest, Hungary, February 27-28, 1994 (Box 16)
  - China's Cultural Triangle IU (& Ohio State) Alumni Tour (John W. Ryan/DPR hosts for IU), September 9-27, 1993 (Box 16)
  - International Association of Universities (IAU): Coimbra/Salamanca Seminar (Portugal & Spain) John W. Ryan speaker., April 18-24, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Hungary Accreditation Committee Advisory board (Prof. Andras Róna-Tás), Feb 26-Mar 3, 1993 (Box 16)
  - United Arab Emirates: 2 Paris, France:, March 22-April 3, 1992; April 3-10, 1992 (Box 16)
  - United Arab Emirates (UAE-University) (Prior Informational Materials), March 22- April 2 1992 (Box 16)
  - Japan/Thailand- (Japan for IUF International Council) (Thailand: John W. Ryan received Honorary Degree from National Institute of Development Administration (NIDA) and for IUF International Council.), March 25-April 5, 1991 (Box 16)
  - Warsaw University, Poland, April 1-5, 1990 (Box 16)
  - United Arab Emirates University (Box 16)
    - Al Ain, United Arab Emirates, March 23-April 1 1990 (Box 16)
    - United Arab Emirates (Abu Dhabi), September 15-24, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Unfoldered Report (Box 16)
    - March 25-April 11, 1989 (Box 16)
- Restricted Files (Box 16)
- Oversized (Box 23)